<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TrafficTicketBuddy Lawyer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="trams_condition"><u>Terms &amp; Conditions</u>.</string>
    <string name="login"><u>Login</u>.</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1915148695450105</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1915148695450105</string>


    <string-array name="gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="about_us_html"><![CDATA[
    <p>Traffic Ticket Buddy is owned and operated by Traffic Ticket Buddy, which is a registered legal document assistant company, that specializes in helping motorists to fight their (country/state) traffic tickets through the Trial by Declaration process.<p>
    <p>We are registered to cover all of states, and we take pride in custom preparing each Trial by declaration defense package by hand. Our goal is to give our customers the best chance to get their tickets dismissed as fast as possible. No points, no school.<p>
    <p>Our experience and excellent track record in providing legal services to motorists charged with traffic offenses like speeding, suspended license and DUI has made us everyone\'s choice.<p>
<p>We make all court appearances for you – so you do not have to go and miss work or spend long hours in line or in court.<p>
<p>We help people with their traffic ticket problems in ALL courts and courthouses in your state.<p>
<h1 style="font-size:15px;"><font color="#109af5">OUR VISION</font></h1>
<p>We never use computer software to generate our defense packages and this is what makes us stand out.<p>
<p>If you have a traffic ticket or warrant out of in (state you cover) or GC Services has sent you a letter charging you a big fine or your license is suspended because of a traffic ticket and you need help clearing it up. We will answer all of your questions and offer advice on how to fix your traffic ticket problem.<p>
<p>At <a href="http://www.trafficticketbuddy.ca" style="color:#109af5;">TrafficTicket</a> Buddy, we work hard to protect your rights!<p>
]]></string>
</resources>
